The Phantom of the Range is a western film directed by James Dugan.
Duke Carlton, an actor stranded in a small western town, gets a job as a cowboy on Tim O'Brien's ranch as a
reward for beating up "Flash" Corbin, a real estate agent who has been trying to swindle the rancher.
A romance develops between the actor and Patsy O'Brien, the rancher's daughter, but it is interrupted by
the appearance of his former stage partner, Vera Van Swank, who claims him as her husband.
He clears himself of the bigamy charge, foils a plot to cheat the rancher
out of a $90,000 land property, and wins the daughter's hand.
Duke Carlton, played by Tom Tyler.
Tim O'Brien, played by Charles McHugh.
Patsy O'Brien, played by Duane Thompson.
Spuds O'Brien, played by Frankie Darro.
'Flash' Corbin, played by James Pierce.
Vera Van Swank, played by Marjorie Zier.
Phantom of the Range is a 1928 American silent Western film directed by James
Dugan and starring Tom Tyler, Frankie Darro and Duane Thompson.
In 1931 it was remade as a sound film The Cheyenne Cyclone.
Tyler also starred in a later film with a similar
title The Phantom of the Range.